<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <array name="cover">
        <item />
        <item>Dear Mr. Anderson, I’m writing in response to your recently advertised position for an IT Analyst role. I am very interested in this opportunity with XXX Solutions and believe that my qualifications, education, and professional experience would make me a strong candidate for the position. I am a highly organized, thorough and motivated professional with over three years experience in an IT role. I am currently employed with Office Tech, a leading company in Brisbane. As I am a fast adaptive professional, I have mastered most of tools and methodologies for analysis and information systems development in different platforms including all published in your advertisement like UML, Enterprise Architect, USE CASE, etc. Enclosed is my resume that more fully details my background and work experience, and how they relate to your position. Job for your company would be the progress in my professional career and I hope I will have the opportunity to present myself on the job interview. I can be reached anytime through my mobile at 555-555-5555 or mail at margret.chan@email.com. Thank you for your time and consideration. I look forward to being able to discuss the position with you further.</item>
        <item>Dear Ms.Janet, l write in response to your ad seeking an Administrative Assistant at Life Style Professional. As a highly competent Administrative Assistant, I would bring a resourceful, flexible, and hard-working attitude to this role. ln my current position, I maintain an exceedingly functional office environment while providing administrative support for a fast-paced production company. I have a capability for problem-solving and work well independently and little oversight. I respond to requests colleagues and clients in a timely manner and an adept at prioritizing multiple ongoing projects. Additionally, I am adept at: • Handling correspondence, reporting, and documents with efficiency and accuracy. • Creating reports and writing documents that support business needs. • Managing day-to-day activities and travel arrangement for professionals. I am a self-starter and excel at inventory management, meeting support, and event planning. I also work well with Microsoft Word, Excel, and PowerPoint, and adapt quickly to new programs. I hope that my experience at Life Style Professional would excel me to give good administrative support and organization to your firm. I have attached my resume and references along with this letter. Kindly contact me at your earliest convenience so we can discuss the position and your needs in detail. Thank you for time and consideration.</item>
    </array>
    <array name="declar">
        <item>I hereby declare that the above-mentioned information is correct up to my knowledge and I bear the responsibility for the correctness of the above-mentioned particulars.</item>
        <item>I hereby declare that the above written particulars are true to the best of my knowledge and belief.</item>
        <item>I hereby declare that the above mentioned details are true to the best of my knowledge.</item>
        <item>I hereby declare that all the details furnished above are true to the best of my knowledge and belief.</item>
        <item>I here by declare that the above furnished information is authentic to the best of my knowledge.</item>
    </array>
    <array name="exp">
        <item>It director – information technology vice president (vp) – chief information officer (cio) information technology senior management, executive position in a leading multinational organization, contributing business value by developing and executing a strategic, long-term vision, while leading the firm to achieve measurable business results and growth, effectively managing the it portfolio of investments. A strong desire to transform “as-is” organizations into “to-be” market and industry leaders. Additional interest in organizations looking to expand their global presence.</item>
        <item>My objective is to leverage my experience while continuing to be challenged. I have 20 years of experience working for service providers delivering marketing intelligence products and services. My background in management, account management, project management and technical process management represent a unique combination of disciplines. Personally, i have the drive and determination to consistently achieve success as a leader in all of the organizations that i have worked with in the past.</item>
        <item>I am a consistent, hard working, highly motivated person. I enjoy working with the public. I feel that i am a friendly, outgoing and dependable person. I feel it is crucial to demonstrate the importance of my job duties and expectations. I am looking to improve my position in the work force, expand my knowledge and skills. I am also looking to establish long term employment in a friendly environment.</item>
        <item>To participate as a team member in a dynamic work environment focused on promoting business growth by providing superior value and service</item>
        <item>Position in human resources, providing opportunity to make a strong contribution by utilizing and expanding upon related education, skills, experiences and capabilities</item>
        <item>Position at a leading organization as a financial analyst or trader and continue my education in the financial field by obtaining the cfa designation.</item>
        <item>To gain long term employment with a company that is on or looking to be on the cutting edge, a company that puts value on people and the products they are promoting. Honest and ethical, i am looking to call this company my family.</item>
        <item>Exploring career opportunities in the to utilize sales, account management and public interfacing abilities in a challenging business development/senior sales management assignmen</item>
        <item>Secure a responsible position in account management and serve as an account representative sharing my breadth of experience and abilities effecting mutual employee and employer growth and success</item>
        <item>To obtain a new business development position by adding value through utilizing my superior knowledge, prospecting and selling abilities in the business to business arena.</item>
        <item>My goal is to become associated with a company where i can utilize my skills and gain further experience while enhancing the company’s productivity and reputation.</item>
        <item>To secure a position with a stable and profitable organization, where i can be a member of a team and utilize my business experience to the fullest.</item>
        <item>To further my professional career with an executive level management position in a world class company. Seek to diversify my skills in another industry and as part of a larger organization. Relocation desirable.</item>
        <item>Position as an engineer or related position which offers key participation, team oriented tasks, immediate challenges, and career opportunity.</item>
        <item>A Graphic Design position for fresh graduate where my advanced graphic and artistic skills can be utilized for making a quality product for customer satisfaction.</item>
    </array>
    <array name="fresh">
        <item>To secure a position with a stable and profitable organization, where I can be a member of a team and utilize my business experience to the fullest</item>
        <item>To further my professional career with an executive level management position in a world class company. Seek to diversify my skills in another industry and as part of a larger organization. Relocation desirable</item>
        <item>To obtain a challenging position in a high quality engineering environment where my resourceful experience and academic skills will add value to organizational operations</item>
        <item>Obtain a challenging leadership position applying creative problem solving and lean management skills with a growing company to achieve optimum utilization of its resources and maximum profits.</item>
        <item>Director of Lean Manufacturing, Continuous Improvement Change Agent, Value Stream Manager, Lean Manufacturing Champion, Process Improvement Manager, Continuous Improvement Leader, Operations Manager and Management Process Improvement Consultants</item>
        <item>To acquire a demanding position as a Management Trainee with HSBC utilizing accounting skills and business education to provide the best level of support to organization</item>
        <item>A position as a Human Resources Intern utilizing and expanding relevant education while providing exceptional HR skills, knowledge and capabilities.</item>
        <item>An able, keen, skilled, and trustworthy individual seeking a computer technician position. Bringing strong computer skills, and personal attributes including devotion, meeting goals, inventiveness, and the aptitude to follow through.</item>
        <item>To obtain a new business development position by adding worth through utilizing my superior understanding, prospecting and selling abilities in the business to business field.</item>
        <item>Expand management responsibilities, perk up organizational ability to go beyond corporate goals, and assist honor all long-standing commitments made to customers, stockholders, workers and the communities in which we live.</item>
        <item>To work as an ophthalmic assistant in hospitals, or with specialized as surgeons or physicians with a specialty.</item>
        <item>Seek to work in a setting that will dare me extra at the same time as allowing me to add to the sustained enlargement and achievement of the organization.</item>
        <item>Get hold of a position that will give me the ability to relate my sales education to a growing industry. Look forward to working with a corporation that promotes superior products and services; and give me with the chance to meet and go beyond assigned sales goals.</item>
        <item>To get hold of a management position, in which I am given the chance to play a direct role in the limitless growth and achievement of solid organization.</item>
        <item>A Graphic Design position for fresh graduate where my advanced graphic and artistic skills can be utilized for making a quality product for customer satisfaction.</item>
    </array>
    <array name="gradientClear">
        <item>@color/gradientClear_c1</item>
        <item>@color/gradientClear_c2</item>
        <item>@color/gradientClear_c3</item>
    </array>
    <array name="gradientCloudy">
        <item>@color/gradientCloudy_c1</item>
        <item>@color/gradientCloudy_c2</item>
        <item>@color/gradientCloudy_c3</item>
    </array>
    <array name="gradientMostlyCloudy">
        <item>@color/gradientMostlyCloudy_c1</item>
        <item>@color/gradientMostlyCloudy_c2</item>
        <item>@color/gradientMostlyCloudy_c3</item>
    </array>
    <array name="gradientPartlyCloudy">
        <item>@color/gradientPartlyCloudy_c1</item>
        <item>@color/gradientPartlyCloudy_c2</item>
        <item>@color/gradientPartlyCloudy_c3</item>
    </array>
    <array name="gradientPeriodicClouds">
        <item>@color/gradientPeriodicClouds_c1</item>
        <item>@color/gradientPeriodicClouds_c2</item>
        <item>@color/gradientPeriodicClouds_c3</item>
    </array>
</resources>
